Very cool looking site. The layout on each of your pages is pretty strong and you did a good job using the CSS grid. The logo that you’ve created looks cool and compliments the rest of the site quite nicely. I like the ambition behind the loading screen although it might make the experience not as great on some devices because it isn’t actually checking how much the page has loaded due to it just being CSS. You’re basically redirecting from one page to another but I like the idea. The inclusion of a form on your contact page is a great idea and I would love to see it functional. Good stuff overall.